Today, we're going to try to open a
Jeweled Lotus. In my hands, I've got two
packs of Commander Masters. Commander
Masters is a massive Magic set with just
like a ton of really cool cards. I'm
opening it on this brand new Fallout
Nuka-Cola playmat that I got while I was
at Gen Con. And if you're wondering why
I'm trying to open a Jeweled Lotus, I
just still think someday, maybe it's
years from now, the card is going to get
unbanned and it's going to be useful
again.
>> [music]
>> And honestly, I don't think I've maybe
ever in my life opened one single
Jeweled Lotus out of one of these packs.
I've opened a lot of the other cool
stuff, like Guardianship, I've opened
more than once, but I don't think I've
maybe more than one time ever opened a
Jeweled Lotus. Especially the cool one,
the textured one. So,
Haunted Cloak, Generous Gift, Crimson
Fleet Commodore, Phyrexian Gargantua,
Tangible Virtue,
Tromokratis,
got that mountain there,
Reliquary Tower. Okay, here's about to
get to the good stuff. Frantic Search,
[music] such sweet pieces of art in this
set. Path of Ancestry, here we go, guys,
onto the rares.
Azusa, okay, solid, very good card,
right? Very playable card.
>> [music]
>> Mangara, the Diplomat in etched foil,
okay. Not that mountain. Exactly what I
was looking for. Taunting Sliver, could
be better. This is a little bit of a
whiff of a pack so far.
Grenzo, Havoc Raiser, gorgeous art on
this card. Looks really cool, not foil,
not textured. And finally, a Spell
Seeker in the borderless foil. Now, I
will say I like this card a great deal.
I play this card in decks, and this
version is really cool. So, that's how
that's how we're starting things off
here. We have one pack left. We are
going to see if we can open something
crazier and bigger in this second pack.
By the way, if you do like the mat that
I'm playing with, if you're like into
this Ultra Pro mat, you can save 10%
using my name, any Ultra Pro purchase
directly from their website. You can
click that link in my bio, Bateman,
uppercase, all one word, to save 10% off
[music] anything that you buy. Big thank
you to Ultra Pro for supporting my
content. Okay, Thriving Heath, here we
go.
Mesa Sire,
Carrion Grub,
Goliath Sphinx,
Foil Guardian, oh man, Bear Claw. Guys,
hit that follow button if you like
content like this. I do a lot of pack
openings, and at some point I may open
the other two packs from this box.
Kodama's Reach, here we go. Path of
Ancestry, again.
Dread Return, All right, you guys ready
for the for the good stuff?
Torrential Gearhulk. Okay, didn't quite
get there on that one. Great card
though, super playable.
Deadly Rollick in the etched foil.
That's not a bad open. That is a that is
a very solid card that will definitely
go into decks. That's really cool. Happy
about [snorts] that one.
Spark Shaper Visionary. Okay.
Undergrowth Stadium. Very playable and
we have one card left here, guys. Give
us something good.
It's a Treasure Nabber. Okay, so I've
had I've I've opened better packs than
these two before, but still, look at all
the beautiful art, guys. There's so many
cool pieces of art in this set.
Unbelievable.